{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ku..ku.noShow..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947678858592","data":{"timestamp":" 947678858592"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_150711"," gameId":" 331acb1c-85c2-4a7c-b878-77f0cba3011a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ku..ku.noShow..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ku_nzi_vye"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ku..ku.noShow..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947678865201","data":{"timestamp":" 947678865201"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_150711"," gameId":" 331acb1c-85c2-4a7c-b878-77f0cba3011a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ku..ku.noShow..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ku_vye_go"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ku..ku.noShow..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947678871798","data":{"timestamp":" 947678871798"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_150711"," gameId":" 331acb1c-85c2-4a7c-b878-77f0cba3011a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ku..ku.noShow..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ku_ng'u_sho"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ku..ku.noShow..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947678878434","data":{"timestamp":" 947678878434"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_150711"," gameId":" 331acb1c-85c2-4a7c-b878-77f0cba3011a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ku..ku.noShow..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mbe_ku_zi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ku..ku.noShow..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947678885026","data":{"timestamp":" 947678885026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_150711"," gameId":" 331acb1c-85c2-4a7c-b878-77f0cba3011a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ku..ku.noShow..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ku_mgo_shu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ku..ku.noShow..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947678891619","data":{"timestamp":" 947678891618"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_150711"," gameId":" 331acb1c-85c2-4a7c-b878-77f0cba3011a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ku..ku.noShow..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ku_mka_ya"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ku..ku.noShow..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947678898216","data":{"timestamp":" 947678898216"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_150711"," gameId":" 331acb1c-85c2-4a7c-b878-77f0cba3011a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ku..ku.noShow..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mcho_mme_ku"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ku..ku.noShow..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947678904805","data":{"timestamp":" 947678904805"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_150711"," gameId":" 331acb1c-85c2-4a7c-b878-77f0cba3011a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ku..ku.noShow..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_pa_wu_ku"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ku..ku.noShow..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947678911402","data":{"timestamp":" 947678911402"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_150711"," gameId":" 331acb1c-85c2-4a7c-b878-77f0cba3011a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ku..ku.noShow..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ku_ru_mli"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ku..ku.noShow..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947678917993","data":{"timestamp":" 947678917993"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_150711"," gameId":" 331acb1c-85c2-4a7c-b878-77f0cba3011a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ku..ku.noShow..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_re_ku_cha"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ku..ku.noShow..9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947678931150","data":{"timestamp":" 947678931150"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_150711"," gameId":" 331acb1c-85c2-4a7c-b878-77f0cba3011a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ku..ku.noShow..9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_re_ku_cha"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947678941300","data":{"timestamp":" 947678941300"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_150711"," gameId":" cbcebb5f-1092-4068-af06-1e3e08d19cb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947678941523","data":{"timestamp":" 947678941523"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_150711"," gameId":" cbcebb5f-1092-4068-af06-1e3e08d19cb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947678942127","data":{"timestamp":" 947678942126"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_150711"," gameId":" cbcebb5f-1092-4068-af06-1e3e08d19cb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947678942208","data":{"timestamp":" 947678942208"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_150711"," gameId":" cbcebb5f-1092-4068-af06-1e3e08d19cb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947678948072","data":{"timestamp":" 947678948071"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_150711"," gameId":" cbcebb5f-1092-4068-af06-1e3e08d19cb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947678960110","data":{"timestamp":" 947678960110"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_150711"," gameId":" d1ee378e-f983-4d7e-97e6-0fa688e1456d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-2-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947678966493","data":{"timestamp":" 947678966493"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_150711"," gameId":" d1ee378e-f983-4d7e-97e6-0fa688e1456d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-2-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947678973730","data":{"timestamp":" 947678973730"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_150711"," gameId":" d1ee378e-f983-4d7e-97e6-0fa688e1456d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_2-5-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947678980325","data":{"timestamp":" 947678980325"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_150711"," gameId":" d1ee378e-f983-4d7e-97e6-0fa688e1456d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_8-5-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947678987847","data":{"timestamp":" 947678987847"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_150711"," gameId":" d1ee378e-f983-4d7e-97e6-0fa688e1456d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_0-9-3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947678994144","data":{"timestamp":" 947678994144"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_150711"," gameId":" d1ee378e-f983-4d7e-97e6-0fa688e1456d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_11-1-3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947679001941","data":{"timestamp":" 947679001941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_150711"," gameId":" d1ee378e-f983-4d7e-97e6-0fa688e1456d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-12-6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947679011884","data":{"timestamp":" 947679011884"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_150711"," gameId":" d1ee378e-f983-4d7e-97e6-0fa688e1456d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-12-6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}